Guide to the Richard M. Peabody Gargoyle Magazine collection, circa 1976-2009 MS2040
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Production files, Circa 1970-1992; MS2040 Series 4
  - Production Files, MS, Unknown, nd, undated (Box 144, Folder 39)
  - Production Files, MS, Dirk H. Van Nouhuys, nd, undated (Box 144, Folder 40)
  - Production Files, MS, Colin David Webb, nd, undated (Box 144, Folder 41)
  - Production Files, MS, Michael White, nd, undated (Box 144, Folder 42)
  - Production Files, MS, Ernest Wichner, nd, undated (Box 144, Folder 43)
  - Production Files, MS, Michael Wilding, nd, undated (Box 144, Folder 44)
  - Production Files, MS, Carl Wilfaud, nd, undated (Box 144, Folder 45)
  - Production Files, MS, W.C. Woods, nd, undated (Box 144, Folder 46)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 5, undated (Box 145, Folder 1)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 6, undated (Box 145, Folder 2)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 7, undated (Box 145, Folder 3)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 8, undated (Box 145, Folder 4)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 9, undated (Box 145, Folder 5)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 10, undated (Box 145, Folder 6)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 11, undated (Box 145, Folder 7)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 12/13, undated (Box 146, Folder 1)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 12/13, undated (Box 146, Folder 2)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 12/13, undated (Box 146, Folder 3)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 14, undated (Box 146, Folder 4)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 15/16, undated (Box 147, Folder 1)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 15/16, undated (Box 147, Folder 2)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 17/18, undated (Box 147, Folder 3)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 17/18, undated (Box 147, Folder 4)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 17/18, undated (Box 147, Folder 5)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 17/18, undated (Box 147, Folder 6)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 22/23, undated (Box 148, Folder 1)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 22/23, undated (Box 148, Folder 2)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 22/23, undated (Box 148, Folder 3)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 24, undated (Box 149, Folder 1)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 24, undated (Box 149, Folder 2)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 24, undated (Box 149, Folder 3)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 24, undated (Box 149, Folder 4)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 27, undated (Box 150, Folder 1)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 27, undated (Box 150, Folder 2)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 27, undated (Box 150, Folder 3)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 27, undated (Box 150, Folder 4)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 27, undated (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 27, undated (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 27/28, undated (Box 151, Folder 1)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 27/28, undated (Box 151, Folder 2)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 27/28, undated (Box 151, Folder 3)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 27/28, undated (Box 151, Folder 4)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 27/28, undated (Box 151, Folder 5)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 27/28, undated (Box 151, Folder 6)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 27/28, undated (Box 151, Folder 7)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 30/31, undated (Box 152, Folder 1)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 30/31, undated (Box 152, Folder 2)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 30/31, undated (Box 152, Folder 3)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 30/31, undated (Box 152, Folder 4)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 30/31, undated (Box 152, Folder 5)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 30/31, undated (Box 153, Folder 1)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 30/31, undated (Box 153, Folder 2)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 32/33, 35, undated (Box 153, Folder 3)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 32/33, undated (Box 153, Folder 4)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 32/33,34, undated (Box 153, Folder 5)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 32/33, undated (Box 154, Folder 1)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 32/33, undated (Box 154, Folder 2)
  - Production Files, Interviews for Gargoyle 32/33, Laurence Gonzales, undated (Box 155, Folder 1)
  - Production Files, Interviews for Gargoyle 32/33, Edouard Roditi, undated (Box 155, Folder 2)
  - Production Files, Interviews for Gargoyle 32/33, Michael Martone, undated (Box 155, Folder 3)
  - Production Files, Interviews for Gargoyle 32/33, Amy Gerstler, undated (Box 155, Folder 4)
  - Production Files, Interviews for Gargoyle 32/33, Sy Gresser, undated (Box 155, Folder 5)
  - Production Files, Interviews for Gargoyle 32/33, Carol Berger, undated (Box 155, Folder 6)
  - Production Files, Interviews for Gargoyle 32/33, Mary Truitt, undated (Box 155, Folder 7)
  - Production Files, Interviews for Gargoyle 32/33, Interview Material, undated (Box 155, Folder 8)
  - Production Files, Interviews for Gargoyle 32/33, undated (Box 155, Folder 9)
  - Production Files, Interviews for Gargoyle 32/33, undated (Box 155, Folder 10)
  - Production Files, Interviews for Gargoyle 32/33, Reviews, undated (Box 155, Folder 11)
  - Production Files, Interviews for Gargoyle 32/33, Reviews, undated (Box 155, Folder 12)
  - Production Files, Interviews for Gargoyle 32/33, Helene Bokanowski, undated (Box 155, Folder 13)
  - Production Files, Interviews for Gargoyle 32/33, Joanne Findley, undated (Box 155, Folder 14)
  - Production Files, Interviews for Gargoyle 32/33, Ann Downer, undated (Box 155, Folder 15)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 35, undated (Box 156, Folder 1)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 35, undated (Box 156, Folder 2)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 35, undated (Box 156, Folder 3)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 35, undated (Box 156, Folder 4)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 35, undated (Box 156, Folder 5)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 35, undated (Box 156, Folder 6)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 37/38, undated (Box 157, Folder 1)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 37/38, undated (Box 157, Folder 2)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 37/38, undated (Box 157, Folder 3)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 37/38, undated (Box 157, Folder 4)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 37/38, undated (Box 157, Folder 5)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 37/38, undated (Box 157, Folder 6)
  - Production Files, Original Works, Gargoyle 37/38, undated (Box 157, Folder 7)
  - Production Files, Page Mechanicals, Gargoyle 15/16, undated (Box 158, Folder 1)
  - Production Files, Page Mechanicals, Gargoyle 17/18, undated (Box 158, Folder 2)
  - Production Files, Page Mechanicals, Gargoyle 19, undated (Box 158, Folder 3)
  - Production Files, Page Mechanicals, Gargoyle 20/21, undated (Box 158, Folder 4)
  - Production Files, Page Mechanicals, Gargoyle 20/21, undated (Box 158, Folder 5)
  - Production Files, Page Mechanicals, Gargoyle 20/21, undated (Box 159, Folder 1)
  - Production Files, Page Mechanicals, Gargoyle 20/21, undated (Box 159, Folder 2)
  - Production Files, Page Mechanicals, Gargoyle 22/23, undated (Box 159, Folder 3)
  - Production Files, Page Mechanicals, Gargoyle 24, undated (Box 160, Folder 1)
  - Production Files, Page Mechanicals, Gargoyle 24, undated (Box 160, Folder 2)
  - Production Files, Page Mechanicals, Gargoyle 24, undated (Box 160, Folder 3)
  - Production Files, Page Mechanicals, Gargoyle 24, undated (Box 160, Folder 4)
  - Production Files, Page Mechanicals, Gargoyle 25/26, undated (Box 161, Folder 1)
  - Production Files, Page Mechanicals, Gargoyle 25/26, undated (Box 161, Folder 2)
  - Production Files, Page Mechanicals, Gargoyle 25/26, undated (Box 161, Folder 3)
  - Production Files, Page Mechanicals, Gargoyle 25/26, undated (Box 161, Folder 4)
  - Production Files, Page Mechanicals, Gargoyle 25/26, undated (Box 161, Folder 5)
  - Production Files, Page Mechanicals, Fiction 84, undated (Box 161, Folder 6)
  - Production Files, Page Mechanicals, Gargoyle, 27, undated (Box 162, Folder 1)
  - Production Files, Page Mechanicals, Gargoyle, 27, undated (Box 162, Folder 2)
  - Production Files, Page Mechanicals, Gargoyle, 27, undated (Box 162, Folder 3)
  - Production Files, Page Mechanicals, Gargoyle, 27, undated (Box 162, Folder 4)
  - Production Files, Page Mechanicals, Gargoyle, 27, undated (Box 162, Folder 5)
  - Production Files, Page Mechanicals, Gargoyle 30/31, undated (Box 163, Folder 1)
  - Production Files, Page Mechanicals, Gargoyle 30/31, undated (Box 163, Folder 2)
  - Production Files, Page Mechanicals, Gargoyle 30/31, undated (Box 163, Folder 3)
  - Production Files, Page Mechanicals, Gargoyle 30/31, undated (Box 164, Folder 1)
  - Production Files, Page Mechanicals, Gargoyle 30/31, undated (Box 164, Folder 2)
  - Production Files, Page Mechanicals, Gargoyle 30/31, undated (Box 164, Folder 3)
  - Production Files, Page Mechanicals, Gargoyle 30/31, undated (Box 164, Folder 4)
  - Production Files, Page Mechanicals, Gargoyle 32/33, undated (Box 165, Folder 1)
  - Production Files, Page Mechanicals, Gargoyle 32/33, undated (Box 165, Folder 2)
  - Production Files, Page Mechanicals, Gargoyle 32/33, undated (Box 165, Folder 3)
  - Production Files, Page Mechanicals, Gargoyle 32/33, undated (Box 165, Folder 4)
  - Production Files, Page Mechanicals, Gargoyle 32/33, undated (Box 165, Folder 5)
  - Production Files, Page Mechanicals, Gargoyle 35, undated (Box 166, Folder 1)
  - Production Files, Page Mechanicals, Gargoyle 35, undated (Box 166, Folder 2)
  - Production Files, Page Mechanicals, Gargoyle 35, undated (Box 166, Folder 3)
  - Production Files, Page Mechanicals, Gargoyle 35, undated (Box 166, Folder 4)
  - Production Files, Page Mechanicals, Gargoyle 37/38, undated (Box 167, Folder 1)
  - Production Files, Page Mechanicals, Gargoyle 37/38, undated (Box 167, Folder 2)
  - Production Files, Page Mechanicals, Gargoyle 37/38, undated (Box 167, Folder 3)
  - Production Files, Page Mechanicals, Gargoyle 37/38, undated (Box 167, Folder 4)
  - Production Files, Page Mechanicals, Gargoyle 37/38, undated (Box 167, Folder 5)
  - Production Files, Page Mechanicals, Gargoyle 37/38, undated (Box 167, Folder 6)
  - Production Files, Negatives, Gargoyle 10, undated (Box 168, Folder 1)
  - Production Files, Negatives, Gargoyle 11, undated (Box 168, Folder 2)
  - Production Files, Negatives, Gargoyle 14, undated (Box 168, Folder 3)
  - Production Files, Negatives, Gargoyle 15/16, undated (Box 168, Folder 4)
  - Production Files, Negatives, Gargoyle 35, 37/38, undated (Box 168, Folder 5)
  - Production Files, Negatives, DC Magazine, undated (Box 169, Folder 1)
  - Production Files, Drawings, Gargoyle, undated (Box 169, Folder 2)
  - Production Files, Negatives, Gargoyle 11, undated (Box 169, Folder 3)
  - Production Files, Printing Plates, Gargoyle 8, undated (Box 169, Folder 4)
  - Production Files, Page Mechanicals, Gargoyle 37/38, undated (Box 169, Folder 5)
  - Production Files, Negatives, Gargoyle 24,32/33, undated (Box 169, Folder 6)
  - Production Files, Negatives, Gargoyle 37/38, undated (Box 170, Folder 1)
  - Production Files, Negatives, Gargoyle 37/38, undated (Box 170, Folder 2)
  - Production Files, Negatives, Gargoyle 37/38, undated (Box 170, Folder 3)
  - Production Files, Negatives, Gargoyle 37/38, undated (Box 170, Folder 4)
  - Production Files, Negatives, Gargoyle 37/38, undated (Box 170, Folder 5)
  - Production Files, Negatives, Gargoyle 37/38, undated (Box 170, Folder 6)
  - Production Files, Negatives, Gargoyle 37/38, undated (Box 170, Folder 7)
  - Production Files, Negatives, Gargoyle 37/38, undated (Box 170, Folder 8)
  - Production Files, Negatives, Gargoyle 37/38, undated (Box 170, Folder 9)
  - Production Files, Negatives, Gargoyle 37/38, undated (Box 170, Folder 10)
  - Production Files, Negatives, Gargoyle 37/38, undated (Box 170, Folder 11)
  - Production Files, Negatives, Gargoyle 37/38, undated (Box 170, Folder 12)
  - Production Files, Negatives, Gargoyle 37/38, undated (Box 171, Folder 1)
  - Production Files, Negatives, Gargoyle 37/38, undated (Box 171, Folder 2)
  - Production Files, Negatives, Gargoyle 37/38, undated (Box 171, Folder 3)
  - Production Files, Negatives, Gargoyle 37/38, undated (Box 171, Folder 4)
  - Production Files, Negatives, Gargoyle 37/38, undated (Box 171, Folder 5)
  - Production Files, Negatives, Gargoyle 37/38, undated (Box 171, Folder 6)
  - Production Files, Negatives, Gargoyle 37/38, undated (Box 171, Folder 7)
  - Production Files, Negatives, Gargoyle 37/38, undated (Box 171, Folder 8)
  - Production Files, Negatives, Gargoyle 37/38, undated (Box 171, Folder 9)
  - Production Files, Negatives, Gargoyle 37/38, undated (Box 171, Folder 10)
  - Production Files, Negatives, Gargoyle 37/38, undated (Box 171, Folder 11)
  - Production Files, Negatives, Gargoyle 37/38, undated (Box 171, Folder 12)
  - Production Files, Negatives, Gargoyle 37/38, undated (Box 171, Folder 13)
  - Production Files, Negatives, Gargoyle 37/38, undated (Box 171, Folder 14)
  - Production Files, Negatives, Gargoyle 37/38, undated (Box 171, Folder 15)
  - Production Files, Negatives, Gargoyle 37/38, undated (Box 172, Folder 1)
  - Production Files, Negatives, Gargoyle 37/38, undated (Box 172, Folder 2)
  - Production Files, Negatives, Gargoyle 37/38, undated (Box 172, Folder 3)
  - Production Files, Negatives, Gargoyle 37/38, undated (Box 172, Folder 4)
  - Production Files, Negatives, Gargoyle 37/38, undated (Box 172, Folder 5)
  - Production Files, Negatives, Gargoyle 37/38, undated (Box 172, Folder 6)
  - Production Files, Graphic, Gargoyle 37/38, undated (Box 173, Folder 1)
  - Production Files, Glass Negatives, Gargoyle, undated (Box 173, Folder 2)
  - Production Files, Photographs and Negatives, Gargoyle, undated (Box 173, Folder 3)
  - Production Files, Negative for Ad, Gargoyle, undated (Box 173, Folder 4)
  - Production Files, Graphic, Gargoyle, undated (Box 173, Folder 5)
  - Production Files, Matted Photograph, Gargoyle, undated (Box 173, Folder 6)
  - Production Files, Matted Photograph, Gargoyle, undated (Box 173, Folder 7)
  - Production Files, Negatives, Gargoyle, undated (Box 174, Folder 1)
  - Production Files, Negatives, Gargoyle, undated (Box 174, Folder 2)
  - Production Files, Negatives, Gargoyle, undated (Box 174, Folder 3)
  - Production Files, Original Drawings, undated (Box 174, Folder 4)
  - Production Files, Negatives, Gargoyle, undated (Box 174, Folder 5)
  - Production Files, Negatives, Gargoyle, undated (Box 174, Folder 6)
  - Production Files, Negatives, Gargoyle, undated (Box 174, Folder 7)
  - Production Files, Cover, Gargoyle 15/16, undated (Box 174, Folder 8)
  - Production Files, Cover, Gargoyle 17/18, undated (Box 174, Folder 9)
  - Production Files, Cover, Gargoyle 5 11, undated (Box 174, Folder 10)
  - Production Files, Layout, Gargoyle, 20/21, undated (Box 174, Folder 11)
  - Production Files, Cover, Gargoyle, 37/38, undated (Box 174, Folder 12)
  - Production Files, Graphics, Gargoyle, undated (Box 174, Folder 13)
  - Production Files, Page Layout, Gargoyle, undated (Box 174, Folder 14)
  - Production Files, Large Cover, Gargoyle 8, undated (Box 174, Folder 15)
  - Production Files, Vol. 15 list of ads, Circa 1980 (Box 175, Folder 1)
  - Production Files, Editorial from Peabody in unknown vol. of Gargoyle, nd, undated (Box 175, Folder 2)
  - Production Files, Reviews from unknown volumes of Gargoyle, nd, undated (Box 175, Folder 3)
  - Production Files, Reviews from unknown volumes of Gargoyle, nd, undated (Box 175, Folder 4)
  - Production Files, Reviews from unknown volumes of Gargoyle, nd, undated (Box 175, Folder 5)
  - Production Files, Miscellaneous Author Biographies, nd, undated (Box 175, Folder 6)
  - Production Files, Interview with Elizabeth Tallent, nd, undated (Box 175, Folder 7)
  - Production Files, Interview with George Myers, nd, undated (Box 175, Folder 8)
  - Production Files, Interview with Crad Kilodney, nd, undated (Box 175, Folder 9)
  - Production Files, Interview with Scott Sommer, nd, undated (Box 175, Folder 10)
  - Production Files, Interview with Joolz, nd, undated (Box 175, Folder 11)
  - Production Files, Interview with Baldwin, T.C. Boyle, Steven Ford Brow and Loris Essary, nd, undated (Box 175, Folder 12)
  - Production Files, Interview with Paul Metcalf, nd, undated (Box 175, Folder 13)
  - Production Files, Interview with Liz Lockhead, nd, undated (Box 175, Folder 14)
  - Production Files, Cover for Gargoyle, Vol. 12/13 and 33, nd, undated (Box 175, Folder 15)
  - Production Files, Loose pages from Gargoyle, Vol. 6, nd, undated (Box 175, Folder 16)
  - Production Files, Loose pages from Gargoyle, Vol. 7, nd, undated (Box 175, Folder 17)
  - Production Files, Loose pages from Gargoyle, Vol. 10, nd, undated (Box 175, Folder 18)
  - Production Files, Loose pages from Gargoyle, Vol. 14, nd, undated (Box 175, Folder 19)
  - Production Files, Loose pages from Gargoyle, unknown Vol., nd, undated (Box 175, Folder 20)
  - Production Files, Loose pages from Gargoyle, Vol. 15/16, Circa 1980 (Box 175, Folder 21)
  - Production Files, Photos for Gargoyle Vol. 32/33, nd, undated (Box 176, Folder 1)
  - Production Files, Page Mechanical, "Man on Moon", nd, undated (Box 176, Folder 2)
  - Production Files, Graphics, nd, undated (Box 176, Folder 3)
  - Production Files, Graphics, nd, undated (Box 176, Folder 4)
  - Production Files, Matted Photographs, nd, undated (Box 176, Folder 5)
  - Production Files, Invoices and Correspondence concerning publications, 1978-1990 (Box 176, Folder 6)
  - Production Files, Graphics, nd, undated (Box 176, Folder 7)
  - Production Files, Bluelines for unknown volume of Gargoyle. nd, undated (Box 176, Folder 8)
  - Production Files, Correspondence concerning last Gargoyle cover, 1982-1983 (Box 176, Folder 9)
  - Production Files, Taplinger Publishing Company Correspondence, 1982-1987 (Box 176, Folder 10)
  - Production Files, New Zealand Embassy Correspondence, 1987 (Box 176, Folder 11)
  - Production Files, Correspondence, 1976-1990 (Box 176, Folder 12)
  - Production Files, Misc. Photos, nd, undated (Box 176, Folder 13)
  - Production Files, Mailing Lists, nd, undated (Box 176, Folder 14)
  - Production Files, Party Invite for Gargoyle, Vol. 35, nd, undated (Box 176, Folder 15)
  - Production Files, Consignment and sales receipts, 1990 (Box 176, Folder 16)
  - Production Files, Ads placed in Gargoyle, nd, undated (Box 176, Folder 17)
  - Production Files, History of Gargoyle, nd, undated (Box 177, Folder 1)
  - Production Files, Peabody Workshop page mechanical, nd, undated (Box 177, Folder 2)
  - Production Files, Ad for Gargoyle, nd, undated (Box 177, Folder 3)
  - Production Files, Ads for Gargoyle, nd, undated (Box 177, Folder 4)
  - Production Files, Ads for Paycock Press, nd, undated (Box 177, Folder 5)
  - Production Files, Ad for Gargoyle, with negs., nd, undated (Box 177, Folder 6)
  - Production Files, Flyers for Gargoyle related events, nd, undated (Box 177, Folder 7)
  - Production Files, Ads for "Kathy Goes to DC", nd, undated (Box 177, Folder 8)
  - Production Files, Correspondence/Ads for University Microfilms International, 1984-1987 (Box 177, Folder 9)
  - Production Files, Reviews of publications by Paycock Press, 1981-1987 (Box 177, Folder 11)
  - Production Files, Press Releases, 1980-1986 (Box 177, Folder 12)
  - Production Files, Gargoyle Bumpersticker, nd, undated (Box 177, Folder 13)
  - Production Files, List of Expenses, 1976-1979 (Box 177, Folder 14)
  - Production Files, List of Subscribers, 1979-1989 (Box 177, Folder 15)
  - Production Files, Maps, nd, undated (Box 177, Folder 16)
  - Production Files, List of 400 most visible living poets in US, nd, undated (Box 177, Folder 17)
  - Reel to Reel Tapes, Gargoyle #28, undated (Box 178, Folder 1)
  - Reel to Reel Tapes, Gargoyle #29, undated (Box 178, Folder 2)
  - Reel to Reel Tapes, Gargoyle #36, Safety Master, Side A 1/2, undated (Box 178, Folder 3)
  - Reel to Reel Tapes, Gargoyle #36, Master, Side B 1/2, undated (Box 178, Folder 4)
  - Reel to Reel Tapes, Gargoyle #36, Safety Master, Side A 2/2, undated (Box 178, Folder 5)
  - Reel to Reel Tapes, Gargoyle #36, Safety Master, Side B 2/2, undated (Box 178, Folder 6)
  - Reel to Reel Tapes, Gargoyle #36, Master, Side A 1/2, undated (Box 179, Folder 1)
  - Reel to Reel Tapes, Gargoyle #36, Master, Side A 2/2, undated (Box 179, Folder 2)
  - Reel to Reel Tapes, Peabody A, undated (Box 179, Folder 3)
  - Reel to Reel Tapes, Peabody B, undated (Box 179, Folder 4)
  - Reel to Reel Tapes, Peabody C, undated (Box 179, Folder 5)
  - Reel to Reel Tapes, Peabody D, undated (Box 179, Folder 6)
  - Cassette Tapes, Be Bop Deluxe Interview, LeFant Plaza, 1976 (Box 180, Folder 1)
  - Cassette Tapes, Garfield Street, Merril Leffler Interview, 1978 (Box 180, Folder 2)
  - Cassette Tapes, Ginsberg Special, WPFW, 3 Parts, 1978 (Box 180, Folder 3)
  - Cassette Tapes, William Clare and Dennis Boyles Interviews, 1978 (Box 180, Folder 4)
  - Cassette Tapes, Mike Horovitz, 1978 (Box 180, Folder 5)
  - Cassette Tapes, Garfield Street, Michael Mooney Interview, 1979 (Box 180, Folder 6)
  - Cassette Tapes, Garfield Street, Michael Mooney Interview, 1979 (Box 180, Folder 7)
  - Cassette Tapes, Garfield Street, Michael Mooney Interview, 1979 (Box 180, Folder 8)
  - Cassette Tapes, Garfield Street, J. Vega, 1979 (Box 180, Folder 9)
  - Cassette Tapes, Mike Brondoli/Steve Ford Brown, 1979 (Box 180, Folder 10)
  - Cassette Tapes, Tina Fulker Interview, 1984 (Box 180, Folder 11)
  - Cassette Tapes, Tina Fulker Interview, Rita Dove Interview, 1984-1985 (Box 180, Folder 12)
  - Cassette Tapes, Sy Gresser Interview, 1985 (Box 180, Folder 13)
  - Cassette Tapes, Michael Martone Interview, 1986 (Box 180, Folder 14)
  - Cassette Tapes, Michael Martone Interview, 1986 (Box 180, Folder 15)
  - Cassette Tape, Gargoyle Mix 1, #34, 1987 (Box 180, Folder 16)
  - Cassette Tapes, Gargoyle Session, Reel 1, 2, 3 and part of 4, 1989 (Box 180, Folder 17)
  - Cassette Tapes, Gargoyle Session, Reel 4, 5, EMAX sequences and "Columbus Day", 1989 (Box 180, Folder 18)
  - Cassette Tapes, Joolz Interview 1 of 2, 1989 (Box 180, Folder 19)
  - Cassette Tapes, Joolz Interview 2 of 2, 1989 (Box 180, Folder 20)
  - Cassette Tapes, Carlo Purcelli Interview, nd, undated (Box 180, Folder 21)
  - Cassette Tapes, Mary Mackey Interview, nd, undated (Box 180, Folder 22)
  - Cassette Tapes, John Gardner and David McAleavey Interviews, nd, undated (Box 180, Folder 23)
  - Cassette Tapes, Mike Horovitz, nd, undated (Box 180, Folder 24)
  - Cassette Tapes, Beth Joselow, nd, undated (Box 180, Folder 25)
  - Cassette Tapes, #28, undated (Box 180, Folder 26)
  - Cassette Tapes, #29, undated (Box 180, Folder 27)
  - Production Files, Tape Cover page mechanicals, for Gargoyle # 28, #29, #34 and Tina Fulker's Tender Hooks, 1986-1987 (Box 181, Folder 1)
  - Production Files, Tape Cover Negatives and receipts, etc., for Gargoyle # 28,#29, #34 andTina Fulker's Tender Hooks, 1986-1987 (Box 181, Folder 2)